{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "Mythology",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who%20is%20the%20king%20of%20the%20gods%20in%20Greek%20mythology%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Zeus",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Poseidon", "Hades", "Apollo"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Mythology",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which%20goddess%20is%20associated%20with%20wisdom%20and%20warfare%20in%20Greek%20mythology%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Athena",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Aphrodite", "Hera", "Artemis"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Mythology",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who%20is%20the%20Norse%20god%20of%20thunder%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Thor",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Odin", "Loki", "Freyja"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Mythology",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who%20is%20the%20Egyptian%20god%20of%20the%20afterlife%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Anubis",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Osiris", "Horus", "Ra"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Mythology",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What%20creature%20has%20the%20body%20of%20a%20lion%2C%20wings%20of%20an%20eagle%2C%20and%20the%20head%20of%20a%20human%20in%20mythology%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Sphinx",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Centaur", "Minotaur", "Chimera"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Mythology",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who%20is%20the%20Roman%20equivalent%20of%20the%20Greek%20god%20Ares%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Mars",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Jupiter", "Neptune", "Pluto"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Mythology",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which%20Greek%20hero%20is%20known%20for%20his%20exceptional%20strength%20and%20completion%20of%20the%20Twelve%20Labors%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Hercules",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Odysseus", "Achilles", "Perseus"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Mythology",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who%20is%20the%20god%20of%20the%20sea%20in%20Greek%20mythology%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Poseidon",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Hermes", "Dionysus", "Hephaestus"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Mythology",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In%20Norse%20mythology%2C%20what%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20end%20of%20the%20world%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Ragnarok",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Valhalla", "Bifr%C3%B6st", "Midgard"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Mythology",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who%20is%20the%20primary%20Hindu%20god%20known%20as%20the%20preserver%20of%20the%20universe%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Vishnu",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Shiva", "Brahma", "Ganesha"]
    }
  ]
}
